Well the first observation is that both equations give us the same line,
首先观察两个方程式得到相同的线段
the line with equation X1+X2=0.
线段的方程式是 X1+X2=0
And the reason for this is that solution
原因在于第二个解法
two is really just a scalar multiple of solution one. So let's see.
实际上只是第一个解法的纯量倍数 那么我们来看一下
Recall that the prediction is a sigmoid of the linear function.
回想一下 预测是一个 sigmoid 线性函数
So in the first case, for the 0.11,
所以在第一个例子中 对于点 (1,1)
it would be sigmoid of 1+1,
可以得到 σ (1+1)
which is sigmoid of 2, which is 0.88.
即 σ 2 等于 0.88
This is not bad since the point is blue,
因为这个点是蓝色的 所以结果不算差
so it has a label of one.
所以标签为 1
For the point (-1, -1),
对于点 (-1,-1)
the prediction is sigmoid of -1+-1,
预测是 σ (-1-1)
which is sigmoid of -2, which is 0.12.
即 σ -2 等于 0.12
It's also not best since a point label has a label of zero since it's red.
因为这个点标签为 0 是红色的 所以结果不是最佳
Now let's see what happens with the second model.
我们来看一下第二个模型
The point (1, 1) has a prediction sigmoid
点 (1,1) 得到预测是
of 10 times 1 plus 10 times 1 which is sigmoid of 20.
σ (10*1+10*1) 也就是 σ 20
This is a 0.9999999979,
结果是 0.9999999979
which is really close to 1,
非常接近 1
so it's a great prediction.
所以这是个很好的预测
And the point (-1, -1) has
对于点 (-1,-1)
prediction sigmoid of 10 times negative one plus 10 times negative one,
σ (10*-1+10*-1)
which is sigmoid of minus 20,
也就是 σ (-20)
and that is 0.0000000021.
等于 0.0000000021
That's a really, really close to zero so it's a great prediction.
非常接近 0 所以这是个很好的预测
So the answer to the quiz is the second model,
所以这个测试的答案是第二个模型
the second model is super accurate.
第二个模型非常准确
This means it's better, right?
也意味着更好 对不对？
Well after the last section you may be a bit
最后一部分后 你觉得有点勉强
reluctant since this hint's a bit towards overfitting.
因为这可能有点过度拟合
And your hunch is correct.
你的预感是正确的
The problem is overfitting but in a subtle way.
这个问题过度拟合 不过程度比较轻微
Here's what's happening and here's why the first model is
这是整个过程 以及第一个模型更好的原因
better even if it gives a larger error.
即使得出更大的误差
When we apply sigmoid to small values such as X1+X2,
我们把 sigmoid 运用到较小值中 如 X1+X2
we get the function on the left which has a nice slope to the gradient descent.
我们得到左侧的函数 可以有梯度下降更好的坡度
When we multiply the linear function by 10 and take sigmoid of 10X1+10X2,
我们把线性函数乘以 10 后得到 σ (10X1+10X2)
our predictions are much better since they're closer to zero and one.
由于它们更接近 0 和 1 所以预测更好一些
But the function becomes much steeper and it's much harder to do great descent here.
但是函数更加陡峭 这里也更难进行较大幅度的下降
Since the derivatives are mostly close to
因为导数非常接近 0
zero and then very large when we get to the middle of the curve.
到达曲线中部时 导数非常大
Therefore, in order to do gradient descent properly,
所以 为了合理使用梯度下降法
we want a model like the one in the left more than a model like the one in the right.
相比右侧的模型来说 我们更想用左侧的模型
In a conceptual way,
从概念上来说
the model in the right is too
右侧的模型非常稳定
certain and it gives little room for applying gradient descent.
很难运用梯度下降法
Also as we can imagine,
同时正如我们想象的
the points that are classified incorrectly in the model in the right,
这些点在右侧模型中分类错误
will generate large errors and it will be hard to tune the model to correct them.
会产生更大的误差 很难调优模型或纠正模型
These can be summarized in the quote by
这可以引用著名哲学家和数学家
the famous philosopher and mathematician BertrAIND Russell.
伯特兰·罗素 (Bertrand Russell) 的名言进行总结
The whole problem with artificial intelligence,
人工智能的整个问题
is that bad models are so certain of themselves,
在于错误模型对自身非常确定
and good models are so full of doubts.
而好的模型充满疑问
Now the question is,
现在问题是
how do we prevent this type of overfitting from happening?
我们如何避免这种过度拟合发生呢？
This seems to not be easy since the bad model gives smaller errors.
由于错误模型提供了更小误差 所以这并不简单
Well, all we have to do is we have to tweak the error function a bit.
我们要做的是对误差函数稍作调整
Basically we want to punish high coefficients.
大体来说 我们想要惩罚高系数
So what we do is we take
所以我们这里要做的是
the old error function and add a term which is big when the weights are big.
利用原来的误差函数 权重大时 添加较大的一项
There are two ways to do this.
两种方法可以做到这一点
One way is to add the sums of absolute values of the weights times a constant lambda.
第一种方法是加上权重乘以常量 λ 绝对值的总和
The other one is to add the sum of the squares of the weights times that same constant.
另一种方法是加上权重平方总和 再乘以相同的常数
As you can see, these two are large if the weights are large.
可以看到 如果权重大 这两个函数都大
The lambda parameter will tell us how much we want to penalize the coefficients.
参数 λ 告诉我们惩罚系数的多少
If lambda is large,
如果 λ 很大
we penalized them a lot.
惩罚会很严重
And if lambda is small then we don't penalize them much.
如果 λ 很小 那么无需对其进行严重的惩罚
And finally, if we decide to go for the absolute values,
最后如果我们想要得到绝对值
we're doing L1 regularization,
可以使用 L1 正则化
and if we decide to go for the squares,
如果想要得到平方
then we're doing L2 regularization.
可以使用 L2 正则化
Both are very popular,
两者都比较通用
and depending on our goals or application,
这取决于我们的目标
we'll be applying one or the other.
我们可以两者选其一
Here are some general guidelines for deciding between L1 and L2 regularization.
对于使用 L1 和 L2 正则化 这里有一些通用规则
When we apply L1, we tend to end up with sparse vectors.
使用 L1 正则化时 我们希望得到稀疏向量
That means, small weights will tend to go to zero.
它表示较小权重趋向于 0
So if we want to reduce the number of weights and end up with a small set,
所以如果我们想降低权重值 最终得到较小的数
we can use L1.
我们可以使用 L1
This is also good for feature selections and
这也利于特征选择
sometimes we have a problem with hundreds of features,
有时候我们会遇到几百个特征问题
and L1 regularization will help us select which ones are important,
并且L1 正则化可以帮我们选择哪一些更重要
and it will turn the rest into zeroes.
然后将其余的变为 0
L2 on the other hand,
而 L2 正则化
tends not to favor sparse vectors since it
不支持稀疏向量
tries to maintain all the weights homogeneously small.
因为它确保所有权重一致较小
This one normally gives better results for training models so
这个一般可以训练模型 得出更好结果
it's the one we'll use the most. Now let's think a bit.
所以这会是我们最常用的 现在我们来思考一下
Why would L1 regularization produce vectors with sparse weights,
为什么 L1 正则化得出稀疏权重的向量
and L2 regularization will produce vectors with small homogeneous weights?
而 L1 正则化得出较小同质权重的向量？
Well, here's an idea of why.
原因是这样的
If we take the vector (1, 0),
如果我们利用向量 (1,0)
the sums of the absolute values of the weights are one,
权重绝对值的总和是 1
and the sums of the squares of the weights are also one.
权重平方的总和也是 1
But if we take the vector (0.5, 0.5),
不过如果得到向量 (0.5, 0.5)
the sums of the absolute values of the weights is still one,
权重绝对值的总和仍然是 1
but the sums of the squares is 0.25+0.25, which is 0.5.
平方总和是 0.25+0.25 等于 0.5
Thus, L2 regularization will prefer the vector point (0.5,
那么 L2 正则化更倾向于向量 (0.5, 0.5)
0.5) over the vector (1, 0),
而不是向量 (1,0)
since this one produces a smaller sum of squares.
因为前者可以得出更小的平方总和
And in turn, a smaller function.
反过来说得到更小的函数